That's what Finally the Weight is Over is like
.  We waited for this for 10 months
.  Little
Mahalakshmi has come to our house and is very happy.   As soon as
the delivery was done, they
brought the baby and brought it to my bedside.   I don't know what to do, but I
cry because I do
n't know what I'll be like when I grow up.   The
first second I saw it,
I felt like I was seeing my father
.  Everyone at home is very
happy.  Because eight years later,
we got a gold bracelet.  She doesn't know
what to do with Naini when she feels lust for her
.  But everyone at home
kept saying it.  From now on,
when you do everything yourself, I wo
n't even look at you.  I was
very brave when I said I wouldn't do all that
.  But after bringing the baby into the room, did you hold her and pretend to be a baby
?  She is very happy when it arrives
.  It was a complete surrender
.  Even though it was only me, I felt like my
sister and I were not just any girl
.
Bad Naini doesn't have that problem.   It's
a big blessing that she has a dad too.
Naini had been asking for Papa from the beginning, and
she was so
happy.  And thank you so much for all your
blessings.